foreign
welcome back to this moneycontrol live
stream you're watching closing bell with
me Nandita kimka and I am yatin Mota
well yatin a very good Monday marvelous
Monday so to say given the fact that the
Nifty has clocked in a triple digit
rally so from uh 18 500 to 18 600 in
just one session correct given the fact
that we saw quite a bit of volatility
for for Nifty to come to 18 500 from 18
300. but of course what was the big news
today was the fact that Nifty Bank hit a
fresh record you know coming very close
to that 18 000 in fact 44 500 Mark I beg
your pardon but you know it took 113
sessions for the Nifty Bank index to hit
a fresh record aside of that you had
quite a few sectors doing well the
metals pack you had you know the auto
pack the banks of course fmcg basket all
these sectors doing well Realty was also
among the top sectoral movers in today's
session uh but I T and energy sectors
towards the end of the day were emerging
as the top laggers of course uh energy
pack was being weighed down by ongc that
had seen a fairly weak quarter on the
back of a one-time hit on its earning
you know so that stock was not doing
well aside of that power grid HCL Tech
dv's labor among the top Nifty losers in
today's session if you look at the
gainers Eminem you know nearly five
percent uh you know that was the day's
high for m m on the back of you know
good set of numbers good commentary
coming in from the management brokerage
is also maintaining a positive view on
the stock so that was the top Gainer
Titan coal India Tata steel SBI among
the other heavyweights in fact ril was
also participating in today's rally well
made and small cap indices were also
holding up showing strength but there
were quite a few movers in the mid cap
space as usual that were reacting to
earnings and new slow I think you want
to talk about some of them so if you
look at the mid cap and the market quite
active in fact both the mid cap indices
small cap and the mid cap for up nearly
half a percent or so if you look at the
trade today Inox win the top Gainer
almost 15 percent up for that one
Mahindra life eight percent up Isis
Lombard Engineers India as well as BHL
where the other gainers as far as Nifty
500 is concerned losing side we had gmr
infra number is disappointed big time
post with the stock was down 10 percent
in City Union bank and Bal Krishna
Industries also because of the fno
positioning or the results whatever you
may say both of these stocks were down
nearly eight percent so lot of results
reaction Nandita and probably we are
ending the results season very very
shortly a few numbers here and there and
probably by first June will be done with
most of them yeah you know Anthony
you're right this week at least we'll
see a barrage of mid cap and small cap
earnings we'll of course be keeping an
eye on that but let's now take a look at
the top stocks that are on our radar
this afternoon are not really reacting
to numbers but news flow that's ICICI
Lombard for you that stock ended Higher
by about eight percent at one point in
time it was up somewhere around 12
percent or thereabouts you know it is
reacting to newsflow that ICICI Bank
will be increasing its take in the
counter from 48 percent to 52 percent
and you know uh out of that four percent
two and a half percent stake will be
increased by September 2024. now there's
a catch here in the earlier ICICI Bank
was looking to decrease its take to 30
percent let me tell the tell our viewers
that in any insurance Venture a bank can
either hold less than 30 percent stake
or more than 50 percent stake so here uh
ICICI Bank had a 48 stake and that stake
had come down to 48 after ICICI numbers
merger with bharti AXA and you know uh
earlier obviously it had a plan to pair
its stake below to below 30 percent and
it had also got the rbi's approval to do
so by September 2024 but now there's a
change on plan it a change in plan it is
going to extend in fact increase its
stake as I mentioned two and a half
percent stake will be increased by
September 2024 and the rest of the stake
later but you know uh if you look at
what the brokerages are saying motilal
Oswald believe that this stake of ICICI
Bank was a major overhang for ICICI
Lombard and now this overhang is out of
the way so it has picked a target of
somewhere around 1400 rupees are
thereabouts when it comes to the stock
you know if you look at the stock P it
is at around 33x motilal oswal is saying
that you know it has seen quite a big
derating ever since this merger happened
so it from 55x it came down to 33x but
even now it is very expensive if you
look at the sector PE and you know when
you look at what Market men are saying
you know Market veterans or a Mukherjee
is saying that ICICI Lombard is a value
in fact a very quality stock that one
must hold and wait for the valuation
crystallized to crystallize basically
going forward so it's a quality stock
one overhang out of the out of the way
we saw an eight percent rally looks like
there is no upside on this stock going
forward yeah and I say it's a bank
clearly if they increase the stake
anytime soon then that there will be a
flip to the share price as well ah but
shifting gears to Auto sector and
Mahindra and Mahindra was the top Nifty
Gainer today ah simple reason being
earnings were good and the management
commentary was good especially with the
tractor segment wherein the management
is expecting to increase market share
more important the CEO also spoke about
how really they will go about the
non-core assets so they have identified
10 to 15 billion dollars worth of
non-core assets and if they are able to
divest that then there could be some
serious upside to the overall valuation
for this clsa has raised the Target on
Mahindra and Mahindra to 1700 almost 100
rupees from the previous Target price
they do believe that the Mahindra and
Mahindra SUV segment should do well and
they will be able to maintain a market
share about 20 percent and that is one
sector and segment which is doing really
well for mahindras also ah the El Nino
concerns regarding the Tractor Sales are
overdone and probably The Brokerage
beliefs and from from here on given the
management commentary strong ah the
tractor volumes also should be
incrementally better than what it was
anticipated due to the El Nino effect so
clearly when it comes to minor and
mendra good quality earnings good
brokerage upgrades as well as the
management commentary also sounding
quite decent right till the stock has
also outperformed its peers of the last
one year and if you look at the price to
earnings ratio it is you know much lower
compared to the sector PE but you know
one interesting fact is that domestic
mutual funds have paid this take by a
little in the last quarter well let's
also take a look at the other stock
that's on my list it's bhel you know
operationally the quarter was very weak
profit has taken a hit in fact even
margins were lower but the stock is up
you know the interesting part is that
the management believes that you know
the outlook for power sector is pretty
buoyant going forward which is why I
think the stock is in the positive uh
interesting to note that clsa has a cell
rating on the stock uh Target price has
been increased marginally but the Target
price by analyst ranges from 34 Rupees
to 85 rupees so it's a wide range yeah
but you know the main fact as to why
brokerage is a little cautious on this
talk is the fact that it is diversifying
away from its key segment which is power
sector and it's going into Railways
defense nuclear power so in the long
term all these boards well but for the
your term the path to profitability
becomes more hazy that's what brokerages
are saying and which is why they are
little cautious and also the fact that
you know execution has been weak and
when it comes to Thermal orders there
has been a delay so these things
according to brokerages don't really
vote very well and they are very less
near-term catalysts for the stock going
forward if you look at the p e ratio
it's at 60 x I think that's higher than
its sector p and over the last one year
the stock has rallied 60 percent so you
know that way stock looks expensive and
uh but one fact is that both diis and
foreign investors have increased their
stake in the last quarter but we'll have
to see how you know all the things that
the brokerages are mentioning boards for
the stock going forward but according to
them the near term path to profitability
is a little hazy but I think clsa always
has been negative on the stock in terms
of the rating and they haven't been able
to really get the stock down if I may
say so because you know antique on the
other hand has a buy rating on bhel with
a Target of 100 rupees because they do
believe that the power sector provides
multiple leg of growth to the you know
business moving ahead 50 of revenues are
expected to come in from the power
segment moving forward and if they're
able to get better margins there which
the management spoke about probably
Market was excited with that particular
piece and despite the sell rating of
clsa and whatever were the results the
stock moved nearly five percent on the
back of good outlook with the management
gave with respect to the power sector uh
that's about bhel but let's move a bit
forward to the Pharma sector where an
orbindo Pharma reported a good set of
earnings wherein investec also has a buy
rating on this one with a Target price
of 560. obviously the stock was under
pressure but it has also already run up
in the anticipation of good earnings if
you look at investec they do believe
that U.S business remains strong margin
Improvement has driven the minor ebitda
beat but if you look at the non U.S
sales they have disappointed a bit arv
sales also continue to remain weak and
as far as other businesses are concerned
they also remain in line so we have
investing which is a buy rating as I
mentioned earlier with the target was a
560 and in general we are looking at
some traction gradually for the Pharma
companies with respect to the U.S
business you look at DB's dv's Labs the
commentary given by Sun Pharma zydus and
now aurobindo probably there is some
pricing pressure agreed about that but I
think all the pressures are gradually
easing if raw material prices come down
probably we could see some improvement
in the Pharma Industries overall gross
margins right you know with respect to
aurobindo the return ratios haven't
really been that healthy I think and you
know it has been bagging a lot of usfd
approvals for its drugs in the recent
past but anything with respect to uh you
know us FDA issues uh with respect to
its API plant or any issues uh going
forward because you know you've seen Sun
facing issues that's the reality with
all these Pharma companies that one of
their plants probably is under official
action initiated status or has a import
alert or has a you know warning letter
that's I think probably a routine thing
yeah you know to deal with the regulator
but yes you know there have been issues
and most of the Pharma companies do face
some issues in some form or the other
but I think in general the Indian
generic business to the U.S has been
quite strong in fact U.S Pharma I don't
I don't imagine that sector without
Indian suppliers so you know we are
quite dominant with respect to the U.S
business and the way we export to the
U.S markets that has been buoyant but
yeah there are always Tailwinds and
Heavens in this sector in either the
regulatory form or in the pricing front
or you know there is some U.S legislator
who probably objects to hydraulic prices
so yes there has been multiple headwinds
in the recent past but now I think a lot
of Tailwinds to the margins given the
fact that raw material prices have been
coming down right
well so those were the stocks on our
radar you think just one and a half
percent away from Life highs hopefully
we'll have to see whether we managed to
reclaim those record highs this week
itself but for now on this good note uh
we would like to take your leave but
thanks a lot for watching but of course
if you have any comments let us know in
the comment section below and of course
keep following money control for all
your news and other updates but for now
it's a good buy from me and I think I'll
be back at 8 30 am tomorrow morning with
all the market action thanks a lot for
watching
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]